干得好
Nice job.
恭喜你下一轮就要开始了
Congratulations, you're
moving on to the next round.
现在你要去现场了
You're now on to the on-site.
现场就是人们在想采访的时候，
The on-site is,
when people think about interviewing,
他们会想到现场，他们认为是粉饰，他们是这么想的。
they think on-site, they think
whiteboarding, that's what they think of.
没有人认为其他步骤。
Nobody thinks that the other steps.
但就像我们之前说的大多数人不会到达现场
But like we said earlier,
most people won't get to the on-site.
即使你这样做也会有点挑战性
Even if you do,
it's going to be a bit challenging and
我们今天要解决这个问题
we're going to try to solve that today.
但是，真正进入现场是一个成就。
But really, getting to the on-site
is an achievement in itself.
你应该为自己感到骄傲即使你把炸弹完全炸了
You should be proud of yourself if,
even if you bomb completely.
没关系我是说
That's okay.
至少你有机会去采访一些很棒的工程师
At least you have the opportunity to
interview with some really good engineers,
但愿这真的是个好工程师
hopefully that really good engineers.
希望你拿走一些东西，你会从中学到一些东西。
And hopefully you take something away and
you learn something from that.
所以如果你这么做了，给自己一个回合。
So if you made it this far,
give yourself a round.
干得好
Nice job.
你把它做成了外面
You made it to the outside.
现在我们来谈谈你想为现场采访准备的事情。
Now let's talk about the things you want
to prepare for, for the onsite interview.
在白板上的纸上编写没有计算机的代码。
practice writing code without a computer,
on a piece of paper on a whiteboard.
如果你有一个，你有一个华丽的房子，或者我不知道的东西。
If you have one, you have a fancy house or
something I don't know.
我在旧金山的小思科合伙人里没有房间
I don't have room in my tiny
San Cisco partner for whiteboard.
所以我在纸上做一些事情。
So I do things on piece of paper.
我们今天要做的所有工作都是在现场进行的。
And all the exercise we're going to
do today during the on-site portion.
我想让你在纸上做一件事因为这就是你要做的
I want you to do on a piece of paper
because that's how you'll be doing it real
生命或白板。
life or whiteboard.
如果你有自己的喜好但这些文件都是为了
If you happen to have one your fancy,
but do all these paper because
一般都不会有电脑帮你没有冬天的
generally there won't be any computers
help you there's no linters.
没有互联网可以向上看，真的会让你减速。
There's no internet to look up and
honestly it slows you down.
写张纸比较灵活，因为我可以画，
Writing a piece paper is more
flexible because I can draw,
我可以把东西交出去，我可以更灵活地思考一下。
I can cross stuff out and
I can think a bit more flexibly.
这就是你要做的事情
And that's what you'd be doing things.
我得到了白板的焦虑
I get whiteboard anxiety.
我知道有人站在那儿看着我
I know someone standing there watching me,
so
最好还是喜欢解决问题，大声说出来。
it's better just to like practice solving
problems and saying them out loud.
另一个提示是要解决常规样本问题。
Another tip is to go over
general sample problems.
有点像我要给你的或者你可以上网查的
Kind of like the ones I'm gonna give
you or ones you can look up online.
练习不带电脑的人
Practice doing those
without a computer and
不要关注解决方案，关注您的情况。
don't focus on the solutions,
focus on how you got there.
我保证你可能不会再看到同样的问题了
Cuz I promise you probably won't see
the same questions over and over again.
你会看到一些你一直没看到的东西
You'll see some, there's always
be something you haven't seen.
重要的是了解如何分解问题和
It's important to learn how
to break down a problem and
说他们在具体问题上找的是什么 ?
say What are they looking for
in the specific problem?
我该如何打破这一问题，我怎么向某人解释呢 ?
How would I break that down,
how would I explain that to somebody?
因为有时你会被困住你会被困住
Because at some point, you're gonna
get stuck, you're gonna get stuck and
你就会被冻结你也不知道下一步该怎么办
you're gonna get freezed, and
you don't know what to do next.
练习帮助缓解其中的一些情况。
And practicing helps
alleviate some of that.
问你的朋友来测试你
Ask your friends to test you.
进行视频交谈，呼叫陌生人。
Do a video chat, call a stranger.
实际上有一些公司会在现场采访你。
There are actually companies out there
that will Live interview you as practice.
利用这一点
Take advantage of that.
这是另一种情况。
It is a different scenario.
你就像我说的
You're like, I aced this.
我把这些问题都解决了
I got all these questions right.
我钉上了他们
I nailed them.
杰姆他不知道他在说话
Jem, he doesn't know he's talking.
我比他聪明
I'm way smarter than him.
这些问题我都解决了没问题
I solved all these problems, no problem.
然后你到白板上面有两个人看着你
And then you get up to the whiteboard and
there's two people watching you and
你就像是
you're like, aah.
如何实施二进制搜索?
How do I implement binary search?
我知道怎么做
I know how to do this.
我以前做过但你只是冻结了
I've done it before,
but you just freeze up.
所以找别人来测试你
So get someone else to test you.
它改变了你对事物的看法
It changes your perspective on
things.And if they will ask what
技术上的问题会是怎样的呢 ?
style of technical questions
Is it going to be?
将会是 Html， CSS，我们正在建造一些东西。
Is it going to be Html, CSS,
we're actually building something.
是否会是高级组件设计，就像我正在设计一个组件，
Is it going to be high level component
design like I'm designing a component that
其他工程师会用吗
other engineers will use?
他们会是算法问题吗
Are they going to be
algorithmic questions?
通常，采访者会告诉你，他们会告诉你要期待什么，
Usually, the interviewer will tell you and
they'll tell you kind of what to expect,
就像一些算法或者他们会有的
like some algorithms some of this or
they'll be.
它们都是你要解决的 JavaScript 问题。
They're all just relevent JavaScript
problems that you're gonna solve.
请尝试提前进行评估。
Try to get assessment ahead of time.
如果它是很多算法，研究算法。
If it's a lot of algorithms,
study algorithms.
如果是很多 JavaScript 问题
If it's a lot of JavaScript questions,
确保你知道 JavaScript 基金会之类的
make sure you know JavaScript foundations,
things like that.
就像这样问一次
Just try to like ask at a time.
如果你知道会发生什么会帮助你摆脱一些紧张情绪
It'll help you get rid of some of
the nervousness if you know what's coming.
这就是你在事业中所做的事情。
So, this is something you
will do in your career.
作为一名工程师
As an engineer.
您可能永远不会进行电话屏幕或必须创建代码测试或
You may not ever do a phone screen or
have to create a code tests or
甚至在电话里找个候选人
even talk to a candidate on the phone.
如果你还没有，你会去采访一个人。
You will interview someone,
if you haven't already.
我真正想让你在采访中消失的是共鸣。
What I really want you to take away
as the interviewer is empathy.
记住接受采访的感觉，记住它的烂程度。
Remember what it's like to interview and
remember how much it sucks.
尽量做尽可能最好的面试的人
And try to be the person that gives
the best possible interview as possible.
是的你可以这么做
Yes, that's possible with you.
你觉得这是完全错误的
You figured it completely wrong,
你想让他们走开那是个好经验
you want them to walk away saying,
that was a good experience.
我学到了一些东西
I learned some things,
显然我有一些学习要做才有资格得到这份工作
clearly I have some learnings to do
before I'm qualified to get this job.
但你想摆脱这种经历吗
But you want to walk away
with that experience?
不是那个 Jen 是个混蛋他根本帮不上
Not that Jen was a jerk,he
didn't help at all,he
一直在电脑上打字
was typing on his computer all the time.
我觉得他在推特上取笑我也许
He's I think he's on Twitter,
making fun of me maybe, like,
是啊我想知道
yeah, which I want to know.
你想让他们
Like, you want them to
有最好的经验，因为采访很烂，我们可以做得更好。
have the best possible experience because
interviewing sucks and we can do better.
只是我们在桌边的另一边
It's just a We get there on
the other side of the table and
就像我们忘记了工作时间里的一切
it's like we forget what it's
like in all the hours of work.
就好像要到这个人去的地方
It's like to get to where this person is.
记住你是七八个人中的一个甚至 10 岁
And remember that you are one of seven or
eight people, maybe even 10 or
他们会在白天跟你说的
20 that they're gonna
talk to you in the day.
所以别试图站出来
So don't try to stand out and
记住采访不是说你有多聪明
remember interviews are not
about showing how smart you are.
你想说这个人很好
You're trying to say is this
person Good to work with.
我是否明白他们的想法 ?
Do I understand the way they think?
我是否同意他们解决问题的方法 ?
Do I agree with the way
they solve problems?
这就是我认为与这家公司合身的一种方式吗 ?
Is it a way that I think will
fit in with this company?
首先要做的是确定这些问题是否与角色相关。
The first thing to do is make sure they
questions are relevent to the role.
这些问题是你必须在现实生活中解决的吗 ?
Are these questions that you've had
to solve in a real life scenario?
如果这样可能是个好问题
If so it's probably a good question.
这些都是你之前要解决的问题。
These are this is a problem
you've had to solve before.
但如果是任意的算法问题如果你想找
But if it's an arbitrary algorithm problem
that's fine if you want if you look for
有人来记忆问题和解决方法但却不知道
someone to memorize problems and
solutions, but it's not gonna really tell
他们怎么想的告诉我他们擅长储存算法
me how they think it tells me they're
good at memorizing algorithms.
我想让你的问题变成边缘案例
I want questions that
you've run into edge cases.
如何呈现具有百万项的列表，或类似的内容 ?
How do I render a list with a million
items, or something like that?
我怎么在这件事上撒尿
How do I paginate something?
我们做的 UI 工程师的事情。
Things that we've done as UI engineers.
这些都与作为一个 UI 工程师有关。
These are relevant to being a UI engineer.
请备份采访者，再次，感同身受。
Have backup interviewers, again, empathy.
他们花了很长时间，工作多，压力很大，
They spend a long time and
a lot of work, and a lot of stress and
如果你想去现场我们就会重新安排
anxiety to get to the on-site If you're
like, we're gonna reschedule because
blahh blahs lahs 生病或反应在最后一分钟
blah blah blahs out sick or
react to pull someone at the last minute
他没有准备好接受他们的首脑们的一个问题
who was not prepared to give
an interview their heads down a problem.
他们会像 JavaScript 面试问题一样去谷歌
They're going to Google some like
JavaScript interview questions
快速备份采访者。
real quick have backup interviewers.
让他们知道他们的支援
Let them know that their the backup or
最好有两个人去面试
have ideally have two
people do an interview.
我总是建议人们
I always recommend to people.
做一个采访因为一个，它消除了偏见。
Doing an interview because one,
it eliminates bias.
我不喜欢那家伙
Two I didn't like that guy.
他是老鹰迷
He's an Eagles fan.
我不喜欢老鹰队
I don't like Eagles fan.
但开发商说，我觉得他们做得不错。
But developers say well,
I thought they did pretty well.
我觉得你有点偏见
I think you have a little bit of bias.
但一般都有两个人
But generally try to have two people.
如果您的公司具有工程规模，可以做到这一点。
If your company has the size
of engineering to do that.
更能让更多的人接受采访
It really helps get up more
even A more even interview.
整日都在书里
Book the room for the entire day.
同样地，你强调了机械师的压力，他们在出汗，
Again, you're stressed out the mechanics
stressed out, they're sweating,
他们很紧张可能是他们的问题
they're nervous, they may have got
the problem right they may have gotten
错了他们还不知道你还不知道呢
wrong they don't know yet
you won't know until finish.
但让他们四处移动和抓住背包之类的东西
But having them move around and
grab their backpack and all this stuff and
转个转
shuffle around.
这不是有用的
That's not helpful.
让他们订白天的房间
Have them book the room for the day.
确保你有充足的时间休息浴室吃午饭
Make sure you have plenty of time for
breaks, bathroom, lunch,
如果他们整天都在那儿
if they're there all day.
确保他们有饮料和零食
Make sure they have drinks, snacks
like anything they need to make them
舒服得像个舒服的人
comfortable as comfortable as possible.
因为面试很烂但你能帮我做得更好
Because again, interviewing sucks,
but you can help make it better
很容易就能友好地提供大量的时间
really easily just by being friendly and
giving plenty of time.
但最重要的是
But above all,
记住，它不是关于你在房间另一边的人的事。
remember, it is not about you is about
the person on the other side of the room.
有句老话说 A 玩家雇佣 A 手
There's an old saying that
A player's hire A players,
B 球员雇用 C 球员， C 球员雇用 D 球员等。
B players hire C players, C players
hire D players and so on and so forth.
因为我们采访的时候，我们经常喜欢这个比我更聪明的人。
Because known when we interview we
often like this person smarter than me.
我很害怕
I am intimidated by that.
当你的自我进入的过程中
As your ego gets in the way, and
我说这些是因为我犯了这一罪，并询问了部落问题。
I say these things because i have been
guilty of this and asked trivia questions.
我过去接受过糟糕的采访，因为我的自我是这样。
I have given poor interviews in the past,
because my ego is in the way.
不你想和比你聪明的人合作
No, you want to work with people
that are smarter than you,
因为他们会让你更聪明
because they'll make you smarter.
他们不会让你看起来很糟
They are not going to make you look bad.
这就是你所担心的，但是他们会让你变得更聪明。
That is what you are worried about, but
they are going to make you smarter.
最理想的是每个人都比你聪明
Ideally, everybody's smarter than you and
他们会帮你加薪因为你想成为最好的采访人
they help raise you up because you want
to be the best interviewer you can.
这就是你参加这个课程的原因吧
That's why you're taking this course,
right?
所以，如果你还记得同情的话，你可以抛弃我所说的所有东西。
So again, you can discard everything
else I've said if you remember empathy.
别忘了它在另一边是什么样的
Just remember what it's like
on the other side of that.
尤其是当你和公司一起工作时
And it's really hard to do especially
when you've been with the company for
几年的时间我都不记得采访的内容
a couple of years cuz you're like, I don't
even remember what it's like to interview.
但如果是这样的话就去面试
But if that's the case,
go out and interview and
记住它是什么样的，你会有更多的感同身受。
remember what it's like, You will
come back with a lot more empathy.